Pavel Kurapatsin

Java Developer

kuropatin.pv@gmail.com +375 44 776-14-71 Mogilev, Belarus



<u>linkedin.com/in/pavel-kurapatsin</u>

github.com/Pavel-Kuropatin

SUMMARY

Goal-oriented person with 1.5+ year of java learning. I continuously study new technologies and able to independently find solutions to emerging issues. I am active and responsible teamplayer. I am passionate about programming and want to develop as a Java developer.

SKILLS

JavaSpring BootSpring MVCSpring Data JPASpring CachesSpring AOPSpring Security BasicsHibernateJDBCSQL/PostgresqlMavenSwaggerJUnit5AssertJMockitoGitGitHubSonar CloudIntellijIDEA

LANGUAGES

Russian - Native

English - C1 (listening, reading), B1 (speaking) | https://www.efset.org/cert/XSSXSK

GITHUB PROJECTS

Booking-App

RESTful Java Web Application powered by Spring Boot

Project created during training at IT-Academy and includes all studied technologies For more information see: https://github.com/Pavel-Kuropatin/Booking-App

EDUCATION

IT-Academy - it-academy.by (04.2021 - 08.2021)

JD2 Course - Java Enterprise Development

Trainer - Viachaslau Kalevich

Self-learning Java (03.2020 - current)

- JavaRush javarush.ru/users/2320603
- Spring Framework <u>spring.io</u>
- Head First Java, 2nd Edition, 2005
- EPAM Java WebDevelopment Conspect, 2015
- Java from EPAM, 2020
- Clean Code: A Handbook of Agile Software Craftsmanship, 2019

Belorussian-Russian University - Master's Degree (2016 - 2018)

Mechanical engineering

Belorussian-Russian University (2010 - 2015)

Mechanical engineering

EXPERIENCE

IT-Academy - Internship (04.2021 - 08.2021)

- Develop RESTful Java Web Application <u>Booking-App</u>
- Learned to develop web applications on Java with modern technologies such as Spring Boot, Spring Data, Spring Security, SQL, Maven, Git

JSC "Soligorsk Institute of Resources Saving Problems with Pilot Production" - Design Engeneer (08.2015 - 12.2020)

- · Development and continious enhancement of pilot production of various equipment
- Perform structural analysis
- Design control of manufactured products
- Participation in research development
- Participation during commissioning and installation of equipment